<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regular Posts on MobliMic.com</title>
    <link>https://moblimic.com/tags/regular-posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regular Posts on MobliMic.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 12:45:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://moblimic.com/tags/regular-posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Weekly&#34; Resource #3</title>
      <link>https://moblimic.com/blog/weekly-resource-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 12:45:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moblimic.com/blog/weekly-resource-3/</guid>
      <description>These &amp;ldquo;weekly&amp;rdquo; resource posts are getting fewer and far between each time I write one. So from now on, I will be changing them by removing the weekly part and instead just make them whenever I think I have found enough content to put in them. Some weeks I come across loads of things that I think are cool, interesting, or useful and others nothing at all.
git pro tip First up a blog post that has helped me a couple of times where I haven&amp;rsquo;t branched before making a commit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Go: CLI Fibonacci</title>
      <link>https://moblimic.com/blog/adventures-in-go-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 22:17:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moblimic.com/blog/adventures-in-go-1/</guid>
      <description>So my &amp;lsquo;first&amp;rsquo; (It&amp;rsquo;s not really my first) adventure in Go I thought I&amp;rsquo;d attempt to make some sort of tool to generate a Fibonacci sequence. The idea is the if I call the program it will give me 10 numbers in the sequence or I can pass it a value and have it return that count of numbers.
It feels sort of overkill but I created a function to accept two ints, add them together, and then return the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Resource #2</title>
      <link>https://moblimic.com/blog/weekly-resource-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 17:42:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moblimic.com/blog/weekly-resource-2/</guid>
      <description>This resource post is very late and very thin on the ground this week! I was at a conference over the weekend so here&amp;rsquo;s a link to the youtube playlist of the videos. There will be some content worth watching in there! I&amp;rsquo;d recommend watching the talk on Empathy-Driven Development when it gets uploaded.
JSConfEU 2018 YouTube playlist
Also here are some links
 Testing for non-testers WCAG 2.1 was published this week  You can find all the weekly resource posts here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Resource #1</title>
      <link>https://moblimic.com/blog/weekly-resource-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 21:50:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moblimic.com/blog/weekly-resource-1/</guid>
      <description>Here begins my first weekly resource post! I&amp;rsquo;ll try to keep doing these regularly but who knows how long I&amp;rsquo;ll keep them up! This week will be a dump of stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve found from the past few weeks. I&amp;rsquo;ve listed a few books I&amp;rsquo;ve read/am reading and some language learning resources etc.
Articles I liked and thought were worth a read  Spend 5 hours a week learning You don&amp;rsquo;t understand your software engineers Why should you learn Go?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>